Finding Aid for Clare E. Hoffman Papers 1934-1962
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Committee files 1947-1962, 8 linear feet
  - 84th Congress 1955-1956
    - Government Operations Committee
      - General (Box 87)
      - Anti-Racketeering (Box 87)
    - Government Information Subcommittee
      - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 87)
      - Press Releases (Box 87)
      - Clippings (Box 87)
    - Intergovernmental Relations Subcommittee (Box 87)
    - Military Operations Subcommittee (Box 87)
    - Public Works and Resources Subcommittee
      - General (Box 88)
      - Al Sarena Mine Investigation, 5 folders (Box 88)
  - 85th Congress 1957-1958
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 88)
    - Government Information Subcommittee, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - 86th Congress 1959-1960
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 88)
  - 87th Congress 1961-1962
    - Government Operation Committee (Box 88)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Lake Michigan Shore Erosion 1947-1952
      - Correspondence and Reports (Box 88)
        (includes photographs)
      - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Reports, 3 folders (Box 88)
  - Photographs
    - Ford Strike 1941 (Box 88)
    - Kohler Strike 1954 (Box 88)
- Scrapbooks 1935-1962, 20 volumes in 5 boxes
  The Scrapbooks series includes clippings documenting Clare E. Hoffman's congressional activities and political campaigns from major daily newspapers. The Volume for 1951 is missing.
  - 1935-1936 (Box 89)
  - 1937-1938 (Box 89)
  - 1939-1941 (Box 89)
  - 1942 (Box 90)
  - 1943 (Box 90)
  - 1944-1945 (Box 90)
  - 1946 (Box 91)
  - 1947 (Box 91)
  - 1948 (Box 91)
  - 1948 Lesinski controversy (Box 91)
  - 1949 (Box 92)
  - 1950 (Box 92)
  - 1952 (Box 92)
  - 1953 (Box 92)
  - 1954 (Box 92)
  - 1955 (Box 93)
  - 1956 (Box 93)
  - 1957 (Box 93)
  - 1958-1959 (Box 93)
  - 1960-1962 (Box 93)